RACING GIRLS COLLAB CAFÉ!
IN PREPARATION
It feels so realistic.
It does!
I didn't know what to expect when you said
you wanted to include one of the vehicles,
but it turned out great. It really brings
the world of Racing Girls to life.
Thank you very much!
What about the merch for that shelf?
It's supposed to be delivered
first thing in the morning.
Is that so?
Senpai?
It's nothing.
What else...
The outfits for the staff
turned out great, as well!
They're so cute.
Does Kamegawa like these kinds of clothes?
Looks great!
I'm looking forward to tomorrow.
Yes, ma'am!
MY AWKWARD SENPAI
EPISODE 8: I'M GONNA BE A MAID!
"I'm Gonna Be a Maid!"
Oh! Senpai!
Oh. Hey.
Good morning.
Are you going somewhere?
Yeah. I'm headed to Kamegawa's job site.
Oh, yeah! Today's the first day for that café!
You look excited for it.
Do I?
Not really.
Can I come with you?
I don't mind, but...
What about your duties?
No worries!
I'll use this as material
for the company newsletter!
I see.
So it's a collaboration with an app game.
Yup.
I put Kamegawa in charge from
the project's proposal stage.
It's his first project,
so I'm sure it was challenging,
but he did his best—
You really are excited for this.
Wha—
You don't have to stare at me like that!
Here's how it is.
Today's the day we see the results of
the job Kamegawa has been in charge of.
Kamegawa sure is lucky.
Huh?
A mentor who puts in this much effort
is hard to come by, you know?
Lately, that guy's been
oozing this happy aura.
Happy aura?
Look at that! Business is booming!
Looks like it.
We can't let our guard down yet,
but it's off to a good start.
But there's still time before
the store even opens.
Isn't everyone here kinda early?
That goes for you, too, Senpai.
The one thing you need for
any opening day is motivation.
That's right!
New software requires automatic
downloads upon pre-order.
And new apps gift items when you pre-register.
I'm not exaggeratin' when I say the battle's
already started before it's even begun!
S-Senpai?
Besides, I need to be prepared as
a senpai. In case something happens.
Well...
he'll probably be all right, since he's
got a good head on his shoulders.
Do you really think so?
Kamegawa can be a bit airheaded at times—
I'm terribly sorry!
I'll make preparations for this immediately.
Please tell me the areas that won't
interfere with your opening tasks.
I'll finish preparing the display right now.
Thank you for helping me.
How did this happen?
The packages arrived just a moment ago.
Weren't they supposed to be here
first thing in the morning?
Apparently, there was a mistake
on the supplier's end.
What? But that's not even your fault.
No. It is your fault for
scheduling things so tightly.
Yes. I'm sorry.
And...
it's also my fault for neglecting to check.
I apologize.
What?
N-Not at all! Why are you
the one apologizing, Senpai?
He's right, Senpai.
Hold on.
Why are you even here, Hotta?
Anyway—
We can discuss this further
once we finish the displays.
There's still time before the store opens.
Yes, ma'am!
I-I've done it now!
When I heard him say the delivery
was due first thing in the mornin',
I kept my mouth shut 'cuz I figured
I shouldn't nag him too much...
I need to actually say what I need to say.
Excuse me, Kamegawa-san?
Yes!
What's the matter?
Three of our part-timers just called out.
What?!
I can contact other employees,
but I doubt they can arrive immediately.
I-I see...
I can reach out to a few event
companies I've worked with before.
I'm so sorry to cause you trouble.
Don't worry about it.
No one could have predicted this.
Thank you so much.
Yeah.
Looks like we can handle
the displays somehow,
but to overcome the lack of
hands on the main floor...
Hotta.
Where's Kannawa-senpai?
It sounds like help will
arrive in the afternoon.
Oh, that's good.
Let's tell Senpai quickly and...
Huh?
She's not here.
Now that I think about it,
she took off over there after
making a serious face.
I knew it! She's furious!
If only I'd done a better job!
Stop moping already.
Regret won't make up for your mistakes.
I know, but still...
Wait, what?
Senpai?
If you have the time to stand around
like that, then plan your next steps.
My next... That's right!
About the additional staff members...
As for me...
If I want redemption...
I'll do anything to achieve it.
What?!
Why are you wearing a maid outfit, Senpai?!
If they're short-staffed,
we should help them.
If I'm to work here,
of course I need to dress like this.
Master's dreams would be
crushed if you didn't, after all.
I-I see...
So stop your brooding.
If you have the time to do that, get to work!
Yes, ma'am! You're absolutely right!
That wasn't it!
C'mon! There must've been
a nicer way to do that!
Hey!
Yes?
All right! I did it!
Senpai! That's not how
you encourage someone!
Welcome home.
Welcome home, Master.
FUEL
Th-Thank you for waiting.
MOE MOE ENERGY CHARGE
SPECIAL RACING RICE
Isn't this supposed to...
F-For victory!
Energy charge of love!
Moe! Moe! Fill 'er up with regular!
I'm terribly sorry! I'll bring you a new one!
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
I really like ketchup anyway.
Then let's begin.
Moe moe rock-paper-scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors... shoot!
MOE MOE ROCK PAPER SCISSORS
WINNER GETS A CLEAR FILE - GET A COASTER IF YOU LOSE
All right! I won!
We got the clear files!
Here you go.
Thank you!
Oh! I got my fave!
See? Look!
Wow! Lucky!
Uh-huh!
I'm terribly sorry!
Oh, that goes over here.
Welcome home, Master!
Here I go!
One, two...
Making a pit stop...
in your...
...heart!
Sh-She's amazing.
She's really fittin' in here.
I guess I'm really not
fit for this kinda thing...
Now ain't the time to feel down!
I need to make sure my junior's
first job is a success!
Um...
Can I ask you a favor?
Finally, break time.
I'm glad the extra help arrived
sooner than we expected.
Thanks for helping out.
No worries. I'm having fun.
Hey.
Do you think Senpai is pushing
herself too far with this?
What makes you think that?
Clank. Clank. Clank.
Because she moves like a robot
every time she walks over to a table.
True.
I'm really sorry.
I'm causing everyone so much trouble...
I don't think she sees it that way, though.
Huh?
I think she wants you to rely on her more.
But this was my mistake, so...
Hmm. How do I put it?
She's even consulted with me,
her junior, about this.
Which proves that she cherishes you a lot.
She consulted with you?
Yup. About this.
But Senpai hasn't mentioned
anything about that...
How could she?
Because if she did, you'd end up worrying.
And now, the moment
you've all been waiting for!
It's time to begin the race!
I'm cutting in!
Clap your hands!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
All together now!
Very good!
Thank you!
RACING GIRLS COLLAB CAFÉ!
OPEN TODAY
We're open today!
RACING GIRLS COLLAB CAFÉ
ONE FREE DRINK
You can get one free drink!
So please take this opportunity to...
Please come visit!
We're the Racing Girls Collab Café!
We're open today!
Senpai!
Please head back to the café
and take a break for a bit.
The stand-in employees are here now,
so I can't have you do all this work...
There's no job out there that I don't have
to do just because I'm your senpai.
But...
Or, what?
Are you saying I'm not capable of
working customer service?
N-No! That's not what I meant.
Please come visit!
I did a lot of part-time work
when I was younger, too!
This is nothing.
Please come visit!
Sorry.
It's nothing!
I'm good.
Here you go, Master!
Thank you!
Please come visit!
Amazing...
Those girls are pros.
Indeed.
Why don't we leave the rest to them
and go take a little break?
Hey, Kamegawa.
What is it, Senpai?
Maids are amazing.
Please come visit!
Here you go.
They are.
I just can't get into character.
Yeah, they're really impressive.
It's also amazing how she's able
to perform so well no matter what.
Do you mean Hotta?
Yeah, she did surprisingly well.
She's ignoring the whole concept, though.
I, on the other hand, haven't done anything.
No! That's not true!
This café was able to open thanks to you.
And the customers genuinely
seem to be enjoying themselves!
I'm so happy that the first job assigned
to me turned out the way it did.
And because you're here, Hotta and
I are motivated to work even harder!
Isn't that just because me
being here puts pressure on you?
What? Um...
HMM...
I can't swim!
Say what?
I-I can only manage 15 meters at best.
When I try to kick my feet, I just sink.
And I still can't eat peppers.
I always procrastinated on my summer
homework until the last day of summer.
I've never won a fight with my siblings.
My hair is super curly.
I frantically straighten it
with an iron every morning!
An iron...
Wait.
When you sometimes show up
with a wavy hair style...
That's not on purpose?
There's no saving it on humid days.
Oh, also...
You have quite the human
side to you after all.
Thanks for saying all that for my sake.
Even so, we can't just keep
resting here the whole time.
I need to perfect being a maid to make up
for how much trouble we caused.
Not that there's gonna be any
demand for me as a maid.
There is!
Huh?
Why did I just blurt that out?
Y-You don't need to worry
about me that much.
That's not what I...
Let's get going.
Like this?
That's not it.
This?
How's this?
Um... Sorry, but...
It's more like this!
Um...
This?
No, like this!
What's she doing?
Is she in a bind?
This is hard...
This!
This?
No!
Like this!
What are you doing to our maid?
Senpai!
Wrong approach!
You're taking the wrong approach!
Thank you!
That's it! That!
Er... Uh-huh...
Wow, I'm so glad I came today! Really!
Oh. I'd like to order a parfait, too.
Oh... Of course.
And also a Moe Moe Rock-Paper-Scissors.
With the same angry energy you just had.
Th-Thank you for your patronage.
Thanks so much for your work today!
The extra girls made it,
so we should be good now.
Again, we're sorry for all the trouble.
Not at all.
Your maid service was amazing, as well!
Thank you very much.
I'm glad the first day went smoothly somehow.
TOUCHING IS NOT ALLOWED!
It's thanks to you, Senpai!
Well, let's head home.
Yes, ma'am!
Hey, about that customer earlier...
Why did he seem so happy about me?
Well, because...
TOUCHING IS NOT ALLOWED!
So that's why!
Do I look like her?
I guess you do have a slight resemblance.
But...
But what?
Er, well...
You seem more like a master
than a maid, I guess.
What's that supposed to mean?
To me, you're my senior,
someone who looks after me in various ways.
So I can't imagine you as someone
who would call another person "Master."
Aren't maids the ones who look after others?
Huh?
I guess you're right.
There you are!
What are you two doing here?
Oh, sorry.
We're just having a little pity party.
Pity party?
What are you saying?
Today was a great success!
We're going to let loose
and go drinking after this!
Hurry and get dressed
before the stores get too busy!
It's time to go, Master!
I-If you're not going, I'm leaving you!
Ah, wait!
Please wait for me!
IF YOU WON'T FOLLOW ME, I'M LEAVING YOU!